ChatGPT. A lot of people are saying, "Oh,
you've got to use this, you've got to use
that." Keep it simple. If there
are competitors and outliers,
sometimes you can
just copy their transcript,
put it into ChatGPT. What
was in this video?
What are the highlights?
Have a little look through.
This means that when you're doing
competitor homework
and looking at what's doing
well for other people,
rather than sitting there through
half-hour videos and
getting bored,
you can nab the transcript from five to 10
different videos, put
them all into AI and go, "What
is the general theme of all of these?"
Then you can
go copy all the comments,
put the comments in there and go,
"What do people like
and dislike about these videos?" Suddenly,
you get your script to your video that
you've planned and made out. You put
that in there and go, from all the things
you've seen in the comments
and all the things there,
is there anything missing
from my video? What would you put in?
Then if you wanted to go a step further,
you could say, "In my writing style, could
you expand into those points
that you thought I should have in my
video?" That's
why I think it's pretty good.